Guide to the New York State Farm Bureau Federation records, [ca. 1918-1968]
New York State Farm Bureau Federation records
- Education - Economics Education of Teachers, 1981 (Box 48, Folder 13)
- Long Island Farm Bureau, 1985 (Box 48, Folder 14)
- Education - Transportation Mileage Limits, 1979 (Box 48, Folder 15)
- Contingency Budgets, 1977 (Box 48, Folder 16)
- Opportunities in Teaching Agriculture, Around 1980 (Box 48, Folder 17)
- Hog Marketing Contacts, 1979 (Box 48, Folder 18)
- Hog Marketing, 1973-79 (Box 48, Folder 19)
- Bidding Requirements for Food, 1980 (Box 48, Folder 20)
- Cornell University, 1981-83 (Box 48, Folder 21)
- Education, 1985 (Box 48, Folder 22)
- Rural Education Groups, 1979 (Box 48, Folder 23)
- Rural Schooling, 1979-80 (Box 48, Folder 24)
- Regents and Education Department, 1978-80 (Box 48, Folder 25)
- Education - Animals, No Date (Box 48, Folder 26)
- Assessment and Equalization, 1980-83 (Box 48, Folder 27)
- Farm Labor Recruitment and Training, 1964-65 (Box 48, Folder 28)
- Multi-State Conference of State Farm Bureaus Board of Directors and Officers, 1968 (Box 48, Folder 29)
  Conneticut, New Jersey, New York, Rhode Island
- New York State Barge Canal System, No Date (Box 48, Folder 30)
  Ronald L. Shelton, Cornell University
- U.S.D.A. - Capper Volstead, 1979 (Box 48, Folder 31)
- Cholesterol Facts, 1976-80 (Box 48, Folder 32)
  Photocopy of the New York Times May 28 1980, An Independent Analysis of the U.S. Heart Disease Epidemic
- Nutrition, 1978-80 (Box 48, Folder 33)
- Northeast Leadership Conference, No Date (Box 48, Folder 34)
- Dog Laws, 1971-78 (Box 48, Folder 35)
- Direct Marketing, 1980 (Box 48, Folder 36)
- Deer Hunting Party Permits, 1979 (Box 48, Folder 37)
- Deer - Destroying Property, 1979 (Box 48, Folder 38)
- Cat Skill Park, 1976-79 (Box 48, Folder 39)
- Empire Livestock, 1977-78 (Box 48, Folder 40)
- Employmnet - Related Housing, 1974 (Box 48, Folder 41)
- Employment of Minors, 1976-81 (Box 48, Folder 42)
- Education - Vocational Agricultural Education, 1969-80 (Box 48, Folder 43)
- Education - School Board Association Bulletin, 1978-81 (Box 48, Folder 44)
- Education - School Financing, 1977-78 (Box 48, Folder 45)
- Department Fees, 1979 (Box 48, Folder 46)
- Education - Retirement, 1977-80 (Box 48, Folder 47)
- Education - Retirement, 1975-79 (Box 48, Folder 48)
- Dealer License Fees, 1979 (Box 48, Folder 49)
- Custon Slaughterers, 1980 (Box 48, Folder 50)
- Covered Dish Suppers, 1978 (Box 48, Folder 51)
- Correctional Facilities Bond Act, 1981 (Box 48, Folder 52)
- College of Agriculture and Life Sciences Budget, 1975-77 (Box 48, Folder 53)
- Civil Service - Tayler Law, 1978-79 (Box 48, Folder 54)
- Children in Harvest of Berries, Fruits and Vegetables, 1975 (Box 48, Folder 55)
- Child Care, 1976 (Box 48, Folder 56)
- New York State School Boards Association Legislative Memos, 1983-86 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  Journal of the New York State School Boards Association, Inc.
- Regents Bicentennial Commemoration of Agriculture, 1983-84 (Box 49, Folder 2)
- National Climate Program, 1978-79 (Box 49, Folder 3)
- Careers in Agriculture, 1976-80 (Box 49, Folder 4)
- Agriculture in the Classroom, 1982-85 (Box 49, Folder 5)
- New York Farm Electrification Council, 1977 (Box 49, Folder 6)
- Reporter - New York State Highway Users, 1975-78 (Box 49, Folder 7)
- New York State Highway Users, 1977 (Box 49, Folder 8)
- Highway Users Conference, 1974 (Box 49, Folder 9)
- By-Laws - New York State Highway Users, 1970 (Box 49, Folder 10)
- New York State Highway Users 1976, 1976 (Box 49, Folder 11)
- New York State Highway Users 1975, 1975 (Box 49, Folder 12)
- New York State Highway Users 1978, 1978 (Box 49, Folder 13)
- Alert - Highway Users Federation, 1977 (Box 49, Folder 14)
- Highway Users Membership Lists, 1978-80 (Box 49, Folder 15)
- New York State Highway Users Association, 1979-81 (Box 49, Folder 16)
- New York State Food Alliance, 1979 (Box 49, Folder 17)
- Farmers and World Affairs, Inc., 1975 (Box 49, Folder 18)
- F.A.C.T.S. (Farmers Agricultural Cooperative Trading Society), 1975 (Box 49, Folder 19)
- Dairylea Cooperative Inc., 1981 (Box 49, Folder 20)
- Rural Manpower Issues - Department of Agricultural Economics, Cornell University, 1977 (Box 49, Folder 21)
- Milk Prices, Marketing, Quality, 1975-76 (Box 49, Folder 22)
- Resource Material - Dairy, 1975 (Box 49, Folder 23)
- Resource Material - Workmen's Compensation, 1945 (Box 49, Folder 24)
- Spotlight - AAMA Processing Vegetable Newsletter, 1976 (Box 49, Folder 25)
- Resource Material - National Boiler Marketing Association, 1978 (Box 49, Folder 26)
- New York Farm Bureau Memorandum of Support, 1981-82 (Box 49, Folder 27)
  Letters sent to various political groups to appeal the farmers' interest at the legislative level
- Monthly Tax Features - Tax Foundation, Inc., 1972 (Box 49, Folder 28)
- State Traffic Safety Council, 1975 (Box 49, Folder 29)
- Accounts Payable, 1977-78 (Box 49, Folder 30)
- Log Times, 1977-78 (Box 49, Folder 31)
- Farm Bureau Memberships, 1977 (Box 49, Folder 32)
- Ocean Data Systems Inc. Minutes of Meeting, 1977-78 (Box 49, Folder 33)
- New York Farm Bureau On-Line Membership System, 1977 (Box 49, Folder 34)
- Financial Department - American Management Association, 1968 (Box 49, Folder 35)
- Fowl Marketing, 1977 (Box 49, Folder 36)
- Farm Credit Service Bank For Cooperatives, 1979 (Box 49, Folder 37)
- Springfield Banks, 1979 (Box 49, Folder 38)
- U.S. Animal Health Association, 1980 (Box 49, Folder 39)
- Orange County - Office of Natural Disaster, 1983 (Box 49, Folder 40)
- American Farm Bureau Federation Aquaculture Advisory Committee, 1980 (Box 49, Folder 41)
- American Farm Bureau Federation Committee - Nomination Forms, 1975 (Box 49, Folder 42)
- American Farm Bureau Federation Commodity Advisory Committee, 1981 (Box 49, Folder 43)
- Commodity - Committee Appointments, 1981 (Box 49, Folder 44)
- Milk Promotion and Research Order, 1979-81 (Box 49, Folder 45)
- Dairy, 1985-86 (Box 49, Folder 46)
- 1980 Milk Promotion Referendum, 1980 (Box 49, Folder 47)
- New York State Milk Promotion Advisory Board, 1977-80 (Box 49, Folder 48)
- Florida Farm Bureau Dairy Replacement, 1978 (Box 49, Folder 49)
- Federal Order No. 2 - New York - New Jersey Milk Marketing Area, 1979 (Box 49, Folder 50)
- Federal Order No. 2 Amendments, 1979 (Box 49, Folder 51)
- East West Dairy Leaders Conference, 1980 (Box 49, Folder 52)
- Department of Agriculture and Markets - Division of Dairy Industry SVCS., 1977 (Box 49, Folder 53)
- Dairymen's Bargaining Act, 1970-71 (Box 49, Folder 54)
- Dairy Task Force, 1979 (Box 49, Folder 55)
- Dairy, Food and Nutrition Council, Inc., 1978 (Box 49, Folder 56)
- Cornell - Bovine Health Research Center, 1979 (Box 49, Folder 57)
- Spot Milk Sales Desk - Feasibility Study 1979, 1979 (Box 49, Folder 58)
- Spot Milk Sales Desk, 1971*- (Box 49, Folder 59)
- New York Cattle Export, 1980 (Box 50, Folder 1)
- Milk Promotion, 1980 (Box 50, Folder 2)
- New England Nutritional Milk Pricing Committee, 1980 (Box 50, Folder 3)
- Milk Reloading, 1977-78 (Box 50, Folder 4)
- Milk Producers Being Dropped By Handlers, 1978 (Box 50, Folder 5)
- Milk Price Report, 1981 (Box 50, Folder 6)
- Milk Marketing (Special) #1, 1978 (Box 50, Folder 7)
- Milk Marketing (Special) #2, 1978 (Box 50, Folder 8)
- Milk Marketing (Special) #3, 1978 (Box 50, Folder 9)
- Milk Marketing (Special) #4, 1978 (Box 50, Folder 10)
- Milk Hauling, 1979-80 (Box 50, Folder 11)
- Congressional Comments - Reconstituted Milk, 1980 (Box 50, Folder 12)
- Base - Excess Plans for Milk, 1962-80 (Box 50, Folder 13)
- Aseptic Milk, 1978 (Box 50, Folder 14)
- American Dairy Association, 1979-80 (Box 50, Folder 15)
- Cheese Facts, 1980 (Box 50, Folder 16)
- Dairy Herd Replacement Program, 1971-77 (Box 50, Folder 17)
- Northeast Slaughter Program, 1976-77 (Box 50, Folder 18)
- Dairy, 1974-77 (Box 50, Folder 19)
- Beef, 1978-81 (Box 50, Folder 20)
- Dairy Economics, 1968-73 (Box 50, Folder 21)
- Dairy Economics II, 1981 (Box 50, Folder 22)
- School Lunch, 1977 (Box 50, Folder 23)
- Dietary Guidelines, 1981 (Box 50, Folder 24)
- School Milk Programs, 1980 (Box 50, Folder 25)
- Reconstituted Milk Community Nutrition Institution, 1978-80 (Box 50, Folder 26)
- District Dairy Meetings 1978, 1978 (Box 50, Folder 27)
- District Dairy Meetings 1980, 1980 (Box 50, Folder 28)
- Dairylea, 1982-84 (Box 50, Folder 29)
- Dairy - National, 1975-83 (Box 50, Folder 30)
- New York - Dairy Council, 1980 (Box 50, Folder 31)
- Carl Martin, 1978-79 (Box 50, Folder 32)
- State Orders, 1975-77 (Box 50, Folder 33)
- Agriculture and Markets - Milk Control, 1968 (Box 50, Folder 34)
- State Milk Marketing Orders, 1968-69 (Box 50, Folder 35)
- Eastern Milk Co-op, 1980 (Box 50, Folder 36)
- Dairy, 1982 (Box 50, Folder 37)
- Imitation Cheese Project, 1978-79 (Box 50, Folder 38)
- Oleomargarine (State Issue), 1982-83 (Box 50, Folder 39)
- Milk Promotion (State Issue), 1978 (Box 50, Folder 40)
- Milk Inspection Programs (State Issue), 1976 (Box 50, Folder 41)
- Milk Marketing Advisory Council (State Issue), 1982 (Box 50, Folder 42)
- Milk Cooperatives (State Issue), 1981 (Box 50, Folder 43)
- Agriculture and Markets - Milk (State Issue), 1977-79 (Box 50, Folder 44)